A reminder, the numbers are very good, so
short term money has moved into that, but I am still
thinking bank sir, good Russia, I will tell
you 37,000, whatever you say, Bank Nifty is going to come,
whether it comes in 15 days or a month, but I have a
friend in the bank and there is a lot in midcap banks,
today the commentary that has come
from Bandhan Bank and Mirchi Matar Microfinance, they
say that landing is dam recovery 72825,
cent and temple tweet 98% stop Bandhan etc
diseases, should I comment on Bandhan, RBL Bank,
IDFC, you will be rewarded
midcap bank, let me give
you an update on Rubaru Circle, I had given you 9350 earlier, I did
95.50,
book profit in that and making ₹2,
you have two pieces of handsome, here I should also say that
U Bank 1035, I deducted 1150 and gave
1185, so probably there are two sides of Micro
Finance Law and Urban Bank Khargone district
level art, if you say so, I will
start, please call from the phone machine  So it will
be called ICICI Lombard Insurance
from the ground and Insurance Guddu Yadav
stream ICICI Lombard and testing
1658 character 215 346 1540 mein take 1510
12 stoploss kisah going back to more than 60
Bahubali my favorite updates UP
Bank of Baroda Bank of Baroda will
give the highest record profit in this quarter
which is your July end episode 220 saadhe
chaurasi mein take that bus stop love 7250
decided to ₹90 ok so Bank of Baroda like this
length definition